<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto">

    <com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout
        android:id="@+id/chatMenuAppBarLayout"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:backgroundTint="@color/md_theme_light_primaryContainer"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.5"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <com.google.android.material.appbar.MaterialToolbar
            android:id="@+id/toolbar"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            app:navigationIcon="@drawable/ic_arrow_left"
            app:title="Terms and Conditions" />

    </com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout>

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:paddingHorizontal="16dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/chatMenuAppBarLayout">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
                android:text="Welcome to Our Abenteuer App! By using this application, you agree to the following terms and conditions:\n\n1. Usage: Our Abenteuer App is designed for parents and teachers to facilitate communication regarding children's activities at kindergarten. You must be at least 18 years old to use this application.\n\n2. User Responsibilities: You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password. You agree to provide accurate and complete information when registering for an account.\n\n3. Privacy Policy: We are committed to protecting your privacy. We collect limited personal information solely for the purpose of providing our services. We will not share your information with third parties without your consent.\n\n4. Intellectual Property: All content provided in Our KinderApp, including text, graphics, logos, and images, is the property of Our KinderApp and protected by international copyright laws.\n\n5. Disclaimer: Our Abenteuer App is provided as is without any warranties, express or implied. We do not guarantee the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of the information provided in the application.\n\n6. Limitation of Liability: Our Abenteuer App shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages arising out of or in connection with the use of the application.\n\nBy using Our Abenteuer App, you acknowledge that you have read and understood these terms and conditions and agree to comply with them. If you do not agree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use the application."
                android:textColor="@color/md_theme_dark_onPrimary"
                android:textSize="16sp" />

        </LinearLayout>

    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>

